A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
"NETFLIX
オリジナルシリーズ"
（小銭の音）
（ゲーム音）
（コントローラー操作音）
All right! Ten wins in a row!
（春雄(はるお)）よし
９連勝決まった！
Now, has my godly technique
この豪指の
春雄のテクニックに―
earned this crowd's adoration?
賞賛の眼差しが
集まってるか？
（見物人達）早く負けろ〜
Come on, already!
（春雄）賞賛の欠片もねえ！
Not an ounce of adoration!
（見物人達）順番回せ〜
Learn to take turns!
（春雄）順番待ちの
プレッシャーが半端ねえ！
The crushing pressure
of the impatient queue!
（見物人達）おお〜
Why're they standing in awe
over there?
（春雄）何で向かいで
湧いてんだ？
（見物人達）女だぞ
It's a girl!
（春雄）スト２対戦台に女？
There's a girl playing Street Fighter II?
ばっ〜バカな
No way!
Isn't she from Class 6B,
same as me?
アイツは確かに俺と同じ
６年２組の大野晶(おおの あきら)！
That girl, Akira Ono!
ザンギッ！
Zangief?
♪〜
ORIGINAL WORK BY RENSUKE OSHIKIRI
New Stranger
〜♪
Round 1
（語り手）湾岸戦争勃発
The outbreak of the Gulf War.
長崎県 雲仙普賢岳 大噴火
The eruption of the Fugendake volcano
at Mount Unzen in Nagasaki.
世間が揺れ動いた1991年
1991: The year that shook the world!
STREET FIGHTER II:
THE WORLD WARRIOR
（見物人達）ぉおおおおお…
マジかよ？
Is this for real?
ええ？
Dang it. Dang it.
（春雄）くそっ！　くそっ！
くそっ！
Dang it!
There goes the 500 yen
I'd for snacks tonight...
夜食用の500円が
ゲッ
（台を叩く音）
（コイン投入音）
（男性Ａ）
お？　またアイツ行くのか
Huh? He's going again?
How many times is that, now?
（男性Ｂ）何回目だ？
（ゲーム音）
Doesn't make sense...
（春雄）ありえない
コイツはこんな所に来る
女の子ではなかったはず
She didn't seem like a girl
who'd come here!
Perfect grades,
adored by everybody...
成績優秀で誰からも慕われ―
and she's from a rich family!
しかも金持ちの娘と
来ている！
オレとは全く違う世界に
生きる人間
Someone who lives
in a world apart from mine.
オレのようにこのヤニ臭い
ゲームセンターで
She's the complete opposite
of a kid like me...
who spaces out playing games
in an arcade reeking of tobacco!
ゲームに没頭する人間とは
程遠い存在だったはずだ
So where did she go wrong
to end up here?
何を間違えて
この世界に降り立った！？
（ゲーム音）
Ｙｏｕ Ｗｉｎ！
You win!
あ！　ぐっ…
No way!
（男性Ａ）２８連勝っ！
なんて強い小娘なんだ！
Twenty-eight wins in a row!
This little girl kicks butt!
（男性Ｂ）このゲーセンの
猛者たちが太刀打ち出来ねえ
Even the arcade veterans
are no match for her!
Move it, kid!
（新ﾌﾟﾚｲﾔｰ）
どけ小僧っ！
I'm up next.
次はオレだ
オレが連勝を止めてやるっ！
I'll break her streak!
（春雄）
稼働時からやり続けてきた
このストリートファイター２
I've been playing Street Fighter II
since its release!
この豪指の矢口(やぐち)春雄も
対戦にかけては自信があった
I, Haruo Yaguchi, had faith
in my godly competitive skills.
I can't believe
まさか
that Ono is making
a mockery of the guys
あの大野が男どもを翻弄し―
with this incredible 28-win streak.
28連勝の偉業を
成し遂げているなんて
しかも ザンギエフでっ！
And what's more?
She's using Zangief!
There're some who still can't even
use the Shoryuken command.
昇龍拳(しょうりゅうけん)コマンドが未だに
出来ない奴もいるのに
But she's using such a tricky move,
出すのが困難な―
スクリューパイルドライバー
レバー１回転パンチを―
the full-circle punch combo,
Screw Pile-Driver!
She's making it look so easy!
いとも簡単に
繰り出してくるっ！
忌々しい
How frustrating!
うぉおおおおおお
After I'd finally broken school rules
and gone all the way across
盛り場に行ってはいけない
学校の目をかいくぐるために
the forbidden busy street into the
next town to find this amazing place...
わざわざ隣町まで来て
ようやく見つけたこの優良店
オレのサンクチュアリッ！
my sanctuary!
She's in here making a mess of my oasis.
こいつはオレの憩いの場を
グチャグチャに乱している！
許すわけにはいかん！
I can't allow this.
オレに残された
この50円で―
So with this, my last 50 yen...
I'll make sure you never
come back here!
お前のハナッ柱を
ブチ折ってやるよ！
（新ﾌﾟﾚｲﾔｰ）くそっ！
Dang it!
（男性Ａ）29連勝だ
That's 29 wins in a row!
One more and she's at 30!
（男性Ｂ）次で30連勝
（ゲーム音）
A NEW CHALLENGER!
Guile vs Zangief
（ゲーム音）
（男性Ａ）おいおい
あのガキまたかよ
What? This kid again?
He doesn't know
when he should give up!
（男性Ｂ）
あきらめの悪い奴だな
（ゲーム音声）
ラウンド１ ファイト
Battle 30
（春雄）
あまりやりたくはなかったが
I didn't want to whip out such a move...
いくら強豪の大野でも
この策にはかなうめえ！
But this'll wipe out even the mighty Ono!
（ゲーム音）
（見物人達）はー
待ちガイル！
Guile-turtling...
Street Fighter II
The World Warrior
（語り手）待ちガイルとは！
Guile-turtling involves
holding the joystick diagonally
斜め後方下に
ガードレバーを入れて―
preparing to use one of two
possible special moves
２種類の必殺技を溜めながら
相手の攻撃を待ち―
while waiting for an opponent's attack.
Using low kick, Sonic Boom,
and somersault kicks,
しゃがみ中キックと
ソニックブーム
it's possible to repel
the opponent's advances.
サマーソルトキックで
敵の攻め手を封殺する―
ガイル禁断の戦法である
It's Guile's forbidden strategy.
It's overwhelmingly effective
when used against Zangief.
特にザンギエフに対しては
圧倒的な強さを誇ったのだ！
（男性Ｃ）待ちガイルかよ
He's Guile-turtling?
（男性Ａ）この小僧
This kid chose the most shameless,
dirtiest method there is!
恥ずかしげもなく―
美しくないやり方を
選びくさった
（晶）うっ…
（春雄）男らしくない戦法と
言われても構いはしねえ
Call it an unmanly way of fighting
if you want.
どんな汚い手だろうが
I'll use whatever dirty trick it takes
to eliminate you!
テメエを排除する！
You win!
（ゲーム音）
Ｙｏｕ Ｗｉｎ！
（男性Ａ）
初めてあの娘が
ラウンドをとられたぜ！
That's the first game
someone's defeated her!
Time 3100
Vital 30,000
Bonus 33,100
（男性Ｂ）
待ちガイルじゃ無理もねえ
Nothing's impossible with Guile-turtling.
（男性Ａ）おいおい
あれを見ろ 片手プレイだ！
Whoa, look at that!
-One-handed play!
-Now he's mocking her?
（男性Ｃ）
ここで舐めプレイか！
（男性Ａ）
あの小僧 余裕なマネを
The kid's acting like it's no big deal!
よっぽどあの娘に屈辱 雪辱
恥辱を提供したいご様子だぜ
He wants to drag that girl
through the mud to vindicate himself.
（春雄）大野…
Ono... I can't let you just run amok
here in this realm.
この世界でのさばらせる
ワケにはいかねーんだっ！
Being clueless in every class...
国語も算数も体育も図工も
家庭科も―
in literature, math, gym, art,
home economics...
何もかもがダメな
俺にとって―
これしかなかっ
This is all I have!
ぐわ！
ぐう…
That's what you get
for playing one-handed.
（男性Ａ）
片手プレイなんかすっから
Now it's tied, one-one.
これで一勝一敗
（台を叩く音）
（男性Ｂ）
片手プレイから
両手プレイに戻しやがったぜ
He's playing with both hands again.
He's honest with himself
but that's lame!
（男性Ｃ）素直な奴だが
ダサすぎんだろ！
Now it's the final round.
だが次の最終ラウンドでも
待ちをやられたら―
If she gets turtled again, it's all over.
ひとたまりもねえ
この娘もとうとう負けて
30連勝ならずで―
Will she lose her winning streak
before clinching 30 wins?
終わってしまうのか！？
（ゲーム音声）
ラウンド３　ファイト！
Round 3: Fight!
（男性Ａ）あの小僧っ！
This kid!
待ちカイル戦法を使わず
堂々と戦う気だ！
He wants to fight fair without turtling!
（男性Ｂ）最終局面になって
正攻法で行くとは―
Now that it's the final round, he wants
to have a clean fight. How manly!
なかなか男らしい男よ！
（男性Ｃ）だったら
最初からやれってんだ
Why didn't he do it earlier?
（春雄）ふふっ
正攻法？
A clean fight?
オレにあるのは勝利への
欲のみ
All I've got is...
a thirst for victory!
（見物一同）投げハメ！？
Throw jank?
（語り手）投げハメとは！
Throw jank is making
your opponent block a weak attack
隙の少ない弱攻撃を
ガードさせ―
その硬値の隙に
投げてしまう戦法
then using that window to throw them.
対処法を知らない相手には
一方的に勝利を奪える
A sweeping victory can be achieved
against an unwary opponent.
しかし対人戦では
トラブルの元となり―
But in a competition,
this forbidden technique can
ruffle feathers
死を覚悟しなければならない
禁断の技である！
so one must be prepared even... for death.
But...
（春雄）だが
相手がこの女とわかれば
knowing that my opponent is this girl...
何も恐れるものは―
I've got...
ない
nothing to fear!
やったっ！
I did it!
（晶）…！　ふん！
（春雄）げふぅっ
（足音）
（春雄）テメエ何しやがるっ
You... What are you--
ゔぉ　ゔぉ　ゔぉ
ゔぉ　ゔぉ
Hey, what are you kids doing?
（店員）こらー
何してるんだー
HI SCORE GIRL
これがこの女との
因縁の始まり
Since then,
our fates have been intertwined.
Yaguchi.
（先生）矢口！　矢口春雄！
Haruo Yaguchi.
これの読み方と意味を答えろ
Read the word and tell me its meaning.
（春雄）ん…　んん？
（ゲンコツ）
Don't pretend you can't read it
due to your poor eyesight.
（先生）読めないのを
視力のせいにするな
I know better.
わかってんだぞ
This character describes you perfectly.
これはお前のことを表す
漢字だ
後で辞書で調べとけえ
Look it up after class.
（笑い声）
（級友Ａ）学力もねぇ
絵心もねぇ！
You can't study or draw.
Your future's bleak.
What are you going to do?
どーすんの？　ハルオ
お前どーすんの
（春雄）ゲーマーとして
食っていきたいと言ったら―
I'm sure they'd laugh if I told them
I want to be a pro-gamer.
笑われるよな
そもそもそれで
食ってけんのか？
Can you make a living that way?
Compared to Haruo,
Ono's future is blindingly bright.
（土井(どい)）春雄にくらべて
大野は将来安泰だな
（級友Ａ）
学力優秀で親も大金持ち
She's a perfect student
and her parents are rich!
しかも 結構かわいいよな
She's even got the looks!
（土井）ああ
まさに高嶺の花
Ah, truly the highest hanging fruit.
周りの女子が
かすんで見えるぜ
The other girls just pale in comparison.
I wonder what she does for fun
after school!
（級友Ａ）学校終わったら
何してあそんでるのかな？
（土井）
かなりの英才教育で―
She has no time for trivial things
because of all her extracurriculars.
遊んでるヒマなんてないって
ウワサだ
ピアノの稽古 茶道に習字
Piano lessons, tea ceremony, penmanship.
オレたちとは
別次元の人間だろう
She's on a separate plane from us.
（春雄）あの女が放課後
何をしているかだって？
You want to know what she does
after school?
ゲーセンにいるんだよっ！
She's at the arcade!
You win!
（ゲーム音）
Ｙｏｕ Ｗｉｎ！
（晶）ふー
She cleared it with Dhalsim?
（春雄）ダルシムで
クリアしたのか
しかもワンコインで
And with no continues.
だが それくらい
オレでもカンタンにっ！
But even I can manage something like that.
あ！
な なんと
劣悪きわまりない筐体
What is this absolute monstrosity?
近所の悪ガキの仕業
Must've been the local punks.
Those little demons!
悪魔の所業！
オドロクべきはこの女
What's really shocking is...
何もかも投げ出したくなる
ようなこの環境で―
even with the horrible condition
of this arcade machine,
よくもワンコインで
ベガを倒せたもんだ
she beat Vega using only one coin!
（晶）ふん
（春雄）くそおぉお
負けるわけにはいかねぇ！
Dang it!
I can't afford to be outdone!
オレもダルシムを使って
ベガを倒すのだ
I'll beat Vega using Dhalsim, too!
I won't be second best
to a girl like that!
こんな女子に先を起こさせる
わけにゃいかねえ！
町内で一番スト２が
上手いのは―
I have to be this town's
prime Street Fighter II player!
オレでなくては
いかんのだっ！
おぉ！
The buttons aren't responding!
ボタンが反応しないだと
All that works is light kick.
生きてるのは小キックのみ
ヨガファイヤーも
ヨガフレイムも出来ない！
I can't use Yoga Fire or Yoga Flame!
How did she beat Vega on this machine?
この筐体でベガを！？
ぁああっ！
（エンジン音）
（ゲーム音）
（晶）ふー
ん
（春雄）てっ
（ゲーム音）
（春雄）ちくしょうめ
Give me a break.
Always looking at me
like some angry cat.
いつもいつも威嚇した
猫の目みたいになりやがる
死ね！　死ね死ね
Die. Die, die.
This is my world.
ここはオレの世界っ！
お前なんかが来る
世界じゃないんだ！
Not a place someone like you could enter.
お？　何見てやがんだ？
What are you staring at?
Do my skills impress you?
オレのこの腕前に
感心しているのか？
Splatterhouse.
スプラッターハウス
とらわれた恋人を
救うために―
This is a horror game
where you don a mysterious mask
to save a lost lover.
謎の仮面をかぶって戦う
ホラーゲームだ
武器はおのや なたに角材
You use axes, machetes,
planks as weapons.
The baddies are zombies, leeches
敵といえばゾンビにヒル
ポルターガイストや
ノコギリ野郎と―
poltergeists and guys with saws!
It's a regular gore-fest!
より取りみどりだぜっ！
うへへへ！
死ねぇ！　死ねぇ！
Die! Die!
（晶）ううう…
（足音）
（春雄）あ　ん？
（晶）ふ…
（春雄）なんだよ？
What is it?
Well?
何？
（足音）
Why are you following me? It's creepy.
（春雄）
なんでついてくんだよ！
気色わりぃ
（晶）うう…
（春雄）う…
でえ！　はあ　はあ…
（春雄）あ！
なんだよぉ！
What the heck! Stop following me!
ついてくんなよぉー
やめろぉぉぉぉ
Stop it!
来るなああああああ
Get away!
結局 何事もなく
家に帰ることが出来たけど
In the end, I made it home safe and sound.
なんだったんだあの女
What was her problem?
（女子１）あれ？
心霊写真見ないの？
Huh? You won't look at the ghost picture?
Cut it out.
（女子２）やめなよォ
She's really bad with this kind of stuff.
この人こういう系
すんごく苦手なのに
（春雄）
もしかしてあいつ
Ah! Could she be...
オレがやってたスプラッタ
ハウスを見て怖くなって―
terrified from watching
me play Splatterhouse
一人で
帰れなくなったのでは！？
and couldn't walk home on her own?
（エンジン音）
（ゲーム音）
（台を叩く音）
（マーくん）ガイルかよ
Guile, huh?
Perfect!
あ～～！
（ミーたん）頑張って
You've got this, Ma-kun.
（台を叩く音）
ガイルガイルガイル
Guile! Guile!
This guy's got quite the temper.
（春雄）すさまじい
癇癪男(かんしゃくおとこ)だぜ
（マーくん）スゲェー！
ウォオ！　マッマジ！
Amazing!
Oh, come on!
（台を叩く音）
あああああ！
（春雄）
こりやあとんでもねぇ相手だ
This opponent might be
more than I can handle.
オレに対する直接的
肉体被害を受ける前に―
Better hold back some punches before
he starts throwing some in real life...
退いとくか
（マーくん）ほらほら
オレが上手いんだぜ！
Take that! And that!
I'm the freakin' best!
（ゲーム音）
Ｙｏｕ Ｗｉｎ！
Wow, Ma-kun!
マーくん すごーい
He wasn't so tough after all.
意外と
大したことない奴だったな
I gave you that win.
（春雄）負けてやったんだよ
ムカツクカップルだぜ
What an irritating couple.
ん？
（コイン投入音）
（春雄）大野
Ono, you're challenging that lunatic?
あの癇癪男(かんしゃくおとこ)に
挑むってのか！？
（マーくん）う！
（台を叩く音）
ぁああああ！
代わって
次は私がやるわっ！
My turn! I'll give it a shot.
（ゲーム音声）
はあ　はあ　はあ　はあ！
She's doing that on purpose...
（春雄）この戦い方
わざとだ
（ミーたん）ムキャー
（台を叩く音）
She's got a temper, too?
（春雄）彼女も癇癪(かんしゃく)持ち
テメエがヒワイな
攻撃で負かしたから―
Hey, you made Mi-tan cry
using all those pervy moves!
みーたん
泣いちゃったじゃねぇか！
えーん　チラッ
Peekaboo.
知らんぶりしてんじゃねえ！
Don't play dumb! Refund our 100 yen
and beg for forgiveness!
オレたちの１００円を
返しながら土下座しろぉっ！
（春雄）ちょっと
Now, hold on.
Don't you think that's a bit much?
そりゃあいくらなんでも
無茶苦茶じゃないですか？
Who the heck are you?
Don't butt in!
なんだテメェッ！
でしゃばりくさって
（蹴る音）
（春雄）ゴハア
Get lost!
（ミーたん）失せろオッ！
（春雄）ゴハァ
（マーくん）
くそ生意気なガキ！
You uppity little brat!
（春雄）ぐぉー
Mess with your elders
and lose everything!
（ミーたん）年上に逆らうと
身ぐるみ剥がされ―
金をとられると
わからせてやる！
Your money's ours now, kid!
モガァ！
（衝突音）
（ミーたん）え？　何っ！？
What-- what are you doing?
何やってんの？
何してくれてんの
どうゆうつもり！？
What have you done?
Who do you think--
ファア！
ほ　ほげげー
You... you...
Too far!
（春雄）やりすぎっ！
やりすぎだぜっ大野っ！
You went too far, Ono!
Shaking the machines for coins?
（店員）
メダル落としくさって
It wasn't me, I swear!
（マーくん）違う違う！
（春雄）くそっこいつと
会うと―
Dang it!
Whenever I'm with her,
something goes wrong!
いつもいつも
ろくなことにならねえ！
(チャイム)
（足音）
（春雄）ぁあー
いきなり降ってきやがった！
Ugh, where did this rain come from?
確かこの近くに
駄菓子屋ゲーセンが…
I think there was a candy store
with games nearby.
くそっくそっ！
Oh, man...
ふぃー
It's really pouring,
it was so sunny around lunchtime.
（店員）滝のような雨だねぇ
昼は晴れてたのに
（春雄）たすかったよ
Made it!
（店員）有り金無くすまで
ここで雨宿りしていいわよー
You're welcome as long as you've got
money to spend.
優しい顔でそんなこと
言うなよ おばちゃん
How can you say that with such
a sweet look on your face, granny?
（春雄）有り金７０円か…
A 70 yen budget, huh?
Not a very promising amount
ここで雨がやむまで
やり過ごすには―
if my goal is to wait out the rain here...
少し心細い金額だぜ
（男子）ハアハア
たすかったー
Thank goodness!
（店員）なんだいアンタたち
ここは雨宿り屋じゃないのよ
Hey, you two, this isn't a rain shelter,
you know.
You going to buy anything?
何か買ってくのかい？
（男子）うぐ
（店員）金がないガキは
とっとと失せなー
Brats with no stacks can hit the tracks.
（男子）くそっ！
Meanie!
（春雄）このババア 鬼だ！
This hag is a demon.
The moment I'm penniless,
I'll be out on the street.
金がなくなれば
たちまち追い出される
（店員）いらっしゃい
Welcome.
あ？
ハァハァハァ
（春雄）またお前か！
You again?
ああ ここに筐体がある事を
思い出した上で来たな？
Ah, you came 'cause you remembered
they had arcade games here.
ホント お前って
学校とは大違いの奴だなぁ
You're really a different person
when you're not at school.
んふー
（春雄）さて
どうしたものか
Now, what are my choices?
The games here are Ghosts 'n Goblins
and Final Fight.
ここにある筐体は魔界村と
ファイナルファイト
長時間プレイするとしたら―
If I'm going for longer play time,
it'd have to be Final Fight.
得意の
ファイナルファイトだろうな
この店は３機設定だから
一層長時間プレイが狙えるし
This shop uses the three lives setting,
so I can really drag that out.
Plus, with Ghosts 'n' Goblins,
it can all be over in an instant.
魔界村は一瞬で終了する
可能性があるからな
持ち金は５０円のみかよ
She's only got 50 yen?
どんだけゲームに
ついやしてんだよ
Just how many games do you play?
まあコイツもオレと
同じ状況ってことか
Well, I guess she's
in the same boat as I am.
（コイン投入音）
（店員）あらいい子ねえー
Now that's a good girl.
Ah, I wanted to play it first.
あぁっ！
オレが先にやろとしてたのに
まあいい
お手並み拝見といこうかな
Whatever.
Guess I'll see what you're made of.
お手並み拝見してるなら
コッチやりなさいな魔界村
If you want to show him that
give Ghosts 'n Goblins a try.
（春雄）
いや 魔界村はやりません
No. I'd rather not play
Ghosts 'n Goblins.
え？
（春雄）あの大野が冒頭で
速攻やられている？
Ono is getting beat up
right out of the gate?
She's already lost two lives
in the flashing basement.
チカチカ光る地下で
２機もやられるとは…
そうか　このゲームに関して
オレの方が上手ってことか
I guess that means
I'm the superior player in this game.
１コインで５面の
ナイフ使いが―
I can make it straight to the fifth stage
with all the knife guys on only a coin.
たくさん出てくる所まで
いけるオレの方が
（店員)
突っ立ってんじゃねえ
殺すぞ ガキが！
Quit standing around
or I'll kill you, kid!
This is one cold-hearted grandma.
（春雄）
なんて心の狭いばーさまだ
わかった　わかったよ
お金つかうよ
I get it, I get it. I'll use some money.
（コイン投入音）
（春雄）よーし
もう見てらんねーからよ
All right, I couldn't bear to watch it.
助け船出したるよ
I've come to save you.
オレのガイでオメーを
５面まで導いてやるよ
I'll carry you to the fifth stage
with Guy.
Try to keep up.
ついてきな！
（ギリギリギリギリ）
You don't need to literally
shake in anger...
（ギリギリギリギリ）
ちょ そこまで怒りに
打ち震えなくてもいいだろ
ああ～
あっ
くうっ
あれ？
コイツ実はうまくねぇか？
What? Is she actually really good at this?
She's playing as Haggar she's whooping
them with her normal attack.
ハガーなのに通常攻撃で
敵をハメてるし―
She's throwing these pile drivers
at the perfect time, too.
パイルドライバーの
繰り出し方も的確だ
あぁーパワーがねえ
肉！
I'm out of power.
Meat!
あ～ 肉っ肉ー
Meat, meat!
は！
（踏む音）
Ouch!
いでぇっ！
何すんだよ！
ドラム缶壊して何が悪いっ！
What are you doing?
What's wrong with breaking the barrels?
おいっ なんか言えや！
Hey, say something!
んっ？
大野が破壊するものから
ダイヤか金塊ばっか出てくる
Huh? Everything Ono destroys
drops a diamond or gold bars.
Ono's score...
大野の点数
Haggar -0   213930
コイツまさか
錬金してんのか？
Could she be alchemizing?
（語り手）錬金術とはっ！
Alchemizing in Final Fight...
ファイナルファイトで
画面にある―
This is when, upon destroying a barrel,
タルやドラム缶などを
壊した際―
you press the jump button
0.033秒後にレバーを
違う方向に入力するか―
or input a different direction
on the joystick
0.033 seconds after hitting the barrel
ジャンプボタンを押すと
一万点アイテムが出現する
to acquire an item worth 10,000 points.
You won't get any weapons
or HP restoration items
武器や体力回復アイテムが
手に入らなくなるが
but this technique is indispensable
when shooting for a high score!
ハイスコア狙いには
欠かせないテクニックだっ！
（春雄）ハイスコアを
狙っていたのか
She was going for a high score...
だからタルを無造作に壊す
オレに怒りを覚えたってのか
That's why she was so angry
when I carelessly destroyed that barrel.
では何故
最初に残り０機になるため―
Then why did she die on purpose
till she had no lives left at the start?
わざと死んだ！？
Only one possibility comes to mind.
考える理由はただひとつ
自分を追い込むためだ
She was putting herself in a corner!
次死んだら
ゲームオーバーという―
She wanted to win under the pressure
of her next death being game over!
プレッシャーに
打ち勝つため！
外はどしゃぶり
Seen as, once the game's over,
she'd be thrown out into the downpour.
ゲームが終われば外に
追い出されるこの状況下で―
Is she...
奴はドMか！？
a masochist?
ふん！
ギャアッ！
Or perhaps a sadist?
それともドＳ！？
（雨音）
（電車の音）
（殴音）
うぐっ
Co-op play from hell, where she gets angry
over the trivial issues.
ちょっとしたことで
怒られる地獄の協力プレイ
I'm just dragging her down,
so maybe it's like PVP to her.
いやオレが足を引っ張るから
非協力プレイか？
ゲームオーバーになれば
間違いなく―
Then, when it's game over, we'll be thrown
into the hell outside and catch cold!
外の地獄に放り出されて
風邪をひくっ！
まさにこれ前門の虎
Stuck between a rock...
後門の狼っ！
and a hard place!
ぬぉおおおお
べぶらっ
うあ！　ぬあ！
Come on! Come on!
（殴音）
のあ！
こんな苦しい
ファイナルファイト―
Final Fight has never been so...
painful...
初めてだ
You can't call this "fun"!
まったくもって楽しくない！
（衝突音）
（晶）ふー
Wow...
（春雄）す　すごい
クリアしてしまった
We cleared it.
オレという足手まといが
いながらハイスコアまで
She even got a high score
while carrying me through it.
But now that we've lost our excuse,
we'll be thrown out for sure.
しかしこれで否応なく―
オレたちは
外に放り出されるわけか
おっ？
（鳥の鳴き声）
晴れてやがる
It cleared up!
すげえ
雨に濡れずにすんだのか
Amazing!
No rain! We won't get drenched.
Thanks to her...
コイツのおかげで
あ
（足音）
TEN YEN EACH
Hey, granny!
おばちゃん
大野っ！
Ono!
For getting in your way.
ジャマしたお詫びだ
もらっとけ
Take one.
なんだ？
両方よこせってか？
Huh, you want both of them?
今日の詫びと―
As thanks for today
この前の礼って事かいな？
and from the earlier incident?
まいっか
Well, why not?
（晶）ふふふん
Hmmm...
（春雄）なんだコイツ
This girl...
へへ お前―
ふぐう
Miss, I've been searching for you.
（爺や）お嬢様
探しましたぞ
ささ 早くお乗りください
Come, come, let us be on our way.
（エンジン音）
一瞬でも
Just for a moment...
あいつに気を許したことが
恥ずかしい
I let my guard down for her.
How embarrassing.
♪〜
〜♪
（春雄）学校からの帰り道は
もちろんゲーセンでゲーム
On the way home from school?
Gaming at the arcade, of course!
家の帰れば帰ったで
家庭用機で―
Once I get back home, it's all
games, games, games.
ゲームゲームゲーム
There's no way a girl from class
would come to visit someone like that.
そんな奴の家に―
クラスの女子が
来るなんてありえねえ
Wait, huh? Ono, why are you...?
って うわっ！
大野 お前なんで！？
♪〜
〜♪
Subtitle translation by
Helen O'Horan